[Killua] Been a while
since I flipped my switch on.
[neck cracks]
[Gon] Scissors!
[gunshot]
[thudding]
[Rammot] Hey there, Colt. Check this out.
It almost feels like I've been reborn!
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
INSPIRATION X TO X EVOLVE
[Netero] There have
already been many casualties.
We will proceed using any means necessary.
Will that be acceptable to you?
[politician] Well, yes, of course.
We wouldn't dream
of telling the experts how to proceed.
All we desire now
is for those dangerous creatures
to be eradicated
as swiftly and humanely as possible.
[Netero] Yes, of course. I understand.
[line disconnects]
So their goal is to eradicate the ants.
Leaving the Hunter Association
to take the blame for the fallout.
I get it.
[keyboard clacking]
[Lin] The hierarchy
inside of a Chimera Ant colony
has five total ranks,
with the queen at the very top.
[both grunt]
[Stick] There's the queen.
Right under her is the Royal Guard,
and then the squadron leaders.
That's correct.
And after the king is born,
the hierarchy will shift, just like this.
[Lin] And afterwards,
all the squadron leaders
will report directly to the queen,
[Spin groans]
No wonder they spread so fast.
[Stick] That's a tall order.
[cell phone vibrating]
Mmm.
[pops]
[Rammot] Look at this! [laughs]
Isn't it just incredible?
[gagging]
[groaning] It hurts!
-Peggy.
-Uh-huh.
Remember when I said
we're capable of anything humans are?
Including this bizarre power?
But… but this is…
You've really been pissing me off lately,
so I won't hold back.
It may need to be quite hard
to take effect.
[Rammot grunts]
[Colt gulps]
[yelling]
[gasps]
This is a message from Hagya.
Capture them.
Dead or alive.
"Pretty good fight," huh? I hope so.
I'd like to agree, but I really doubt
they're gonna be much help.
[Leol] I'm fine with that.
You are? Why's that?
Because they'll buy a little time
until we can get there.
[Hina] Oh. I see.
Well, if that's the case, then the Rares
will be ours for the taking.
[Leol grunts] Exactly.
[Kite] We're surrounded.
And by a lot of them, too.
[gasps]
Three, surrender and let us capture you.
You may even survive.
I don't recommend the second option.
If that is the choice you make,
you will only anger us,
Now then, what will you do?
[Gon] Kite.
We couldn't have asked for a better deal.
[boys grunt]
[both] Show me rock!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay. I'm going first.
I only hope that we'll be able
to take full advantage of that.
Number six.
It's six! who has it?
[Baro laughs] Lucky me.
[Baro] Huh? It's obvious, isn't it?
Whoever dies loses.
Are you crazy, kid?
If you lose, then we're just
gonna feed you to the Queen.
Fine. I can agree to that.
But you don't have to die
if you're the one who ends up losing this.
-If i win, I'm not gonna eat you.
-[growling]
Damn it! You dodged that one.
All right, fine!
Then how about this?
[Killua] The same attack?
Whatever. I could keep this up
all day long,
but you'll never be able
to dodge my homing attacks.
[Kite] He's right.
He only has to change his course
to match the direction Gon dodges.
Well, Gon, what will you do?
Listen up. There's something
you should know before you die.
The main reason that we kill humans
isn't so we can eat them ourselves,
or even so we can feed them to the Queen.
[yelling]
[screaming]
Who's my opponent?
Number three. Number three's up!
Settle down.
You're too cocky for your own good.
I'm about to show you
what hell looks like.
Got that? Don't lump me in
with trash like him.
[grunts]
Come on. I'm at least
ten times stronger than that guy.
[Killua] Okay. So, not much, then.
They're suited for this.
Gon's slow start
does make me a bit anxious.
It's like I'm missing something.
There's a gnawing anxiety
that won't go away.
[Rammot] Check this out, Peggy!
[scoffs]
-You're such a stiff, you know that?
-[slap]
Give me a break.
[Colt] Zazan… [breathing heavily]
A few days ago, she told me
that she had captured a Rare.
[breathing heavily]
If we're lucky,
he might still be in the storeroom.
Find it, and secure it.
Keep it up. I can take as many
of those attacks as you've got.
Oh, really?
[grunting, groaning]
[groans]
[all murmuring]
[Kite] What a pleasant surprise.
Their officers can be dispatched easily.
Maybe I'm worrying over nothing.
Let's find out.
-[can rattling]
-[Frog] That's enough. It's my turn.
[Killua] Mmm. That scythe, it's bad news.
[both gasp]
[Frog whimpers] What is this?
Why do I feel so scared?
Yes, that's right.
I think I've experienced
this sensation before.
I remember now.
[Queen bites]
[Killua] Yeah, so why did you
make it that way?
[Kite] Be careful as we advance.
Like I told you before,
they're still alive for a little while.
You okay?
Because it's only going to get worse
from here on.
If you're thinking about the enemy,
you won't be able to last mentally.
I'm all right.
I don't have any sympathy for guys
like him who call each other trash.
[Kite] That's the problem.
with one singular mission on their minds:
Preventing the birth of the king.
[Leol grunts]
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] Next time, "A Fated Awakening".
-[Killua] I'll go.
-[Gon] No, I will.
-[Killua] No, me!
-[Hina] Then I'll go.
[Gon and Killua] Oh, please, go ahead.
[singer singing in Japanese]